Seino! Rattle channel GOGO!
Yes, so today we will be doing a silent dance!
I know everyone has already taken pictures beforehand, but which song is it this time! Here we go!
Let's take a look at it right away!
Okay, let's start the video!
First of all, first of all, first of all!
First of all, yes!
Here you go!
You see that staff member in the black dress over there?
We shot this in the next room, right?
It was a perfect fit.
I'm so glad you said it was a perfect fit! I'm so happy!
And then I told the staff outside.
It's perfect! Isn't it good? I said.
I'm telling everyone.
Clear!
I've been told!
They told me!
Why?
What is this?
I said yes, and that was it.
But every time you say it, it's not right.
Oh, I see.
I don't know.
It's not good.
Reflective, too. It's perfect!
But are you sure you're checking the camera?
Yes!
It's totally, totally, totally perfect!
You don't even know what you're doing here.
Well, then, who really fits?
So what we don't know is...
Maybe they all fit.
Maybe they are.
Maybe we really do fit this time.
Let's believe it, people!
Let's believe!
I heard Towa is doing well.
What? What's the opposite?
Are you good?
Yeah, Tova, I'm good.
What do you mean?
Why are you good?
I think you're the best fit.
Isn't that very promising?
I don't know.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Wait, wait, wait.
Which way? Which way?
This way!
Aah!
There. That's the train.
Oh, my God, you're so superstitious.
Oh, my God!
Come on!
Oh!
Whoa!
What? It fits!
South is so right.
Oh, my God! The sides match! So much!
I love it!
Me too!
Isn't it great?
It's late snowing.
Oh, man! We're late!
You're early!
Early!
Aah! Early!
Fast!
Oh, that's good!
Oh, yeah! We're so together! Wait!
Hey!
You're late!
A little late, isn't it?
Kira, you're late!
Are you early, Momochan?
You're so fast!
You're early!
So fast!
How did it come apart like this?
Stop it!
Yes!
What? So fast! Suddenly!
Pass him suddenly!
Pass him quickly!
Pass him!
I can't see! I can't see! I can't see!
Are you sure?
Seriously?
Please, please, please, it's good!
Wrong, wrong, wrong!
What are you talking about? You're not saying anything else!
Volume! Volume! Volume!
Volume!
Isn't this the place?
I said volume, guys!
Oh, no, don't turn it up that high!
A little too loud?
Just a little bit now.
Yes!
You see that?
Let's roll it up.
What? No one's got it right!
Not in focus at all?
What's out of focus!
Who's out of focus? What?
Does he like you?
And then there's the quest.
You're scaring me.
Momochan!
Momochan, four times already.
No, no, no!
Soon it'll be super fast
So fast!
It's over.
It's too soon.
How did you do it?
I've done it four times with Momo.
You're so late, Mi-chan.
A little late.
Oh, no, no, no, no! Stop it, stop it!
You're so cute!
Someone's dancing moistly.
That's kind of cute.
Four times fast.
Oh, that's so sad.
Not at all.
I'm already here, and it's the Cure.
Frog, you're early!
Cure, you're so late!
What should I do?
Frogs are here.
Nobody's here.
Nobody's early.
Oh, we're all here.
It's all here.
We're all here.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Top of the line.
Oh, they're going to disappear.
I'm moving with you.
Oh, shit.
Okay, this is definitely going to be the killer's last solo act.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
Looks like it's over.
Yes, theme.
Let's be glad and happy about it.
It's done.
Go, go away.
Get out.
Come on.
There's some youth left in there.
They're so happy, aren't they?
Yeah, they are.
What a perfect fit.
It's perfect.
What's wrong with that?
It's nothing.
It's just that last look of happiness on everyone's face.
I want everyone to see it.
Let's see the last one.
It's pretty long at the end.
The yokan will be the first to finish.
They're so happy.
He's like, "Yay!
It's so fast.
Is it done?
Yeah!
She looks so happy.
No, not at all.
He's so happy.
What's next?
They didn't tell you I can tell by the expressions on their faces?
I guess we're about the same.
Misamomoka.
This is for parallel measures.
It's embarrassing.
They don't match at all.
Both of you.
How's it going?
Oh, no, no, no.
Masachan's looking good.
You're cute, Misachan.
She's back.
She's so happy to be back.
But she's smiling.
What's next?
Cleo.
Toreo Cleo.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Claire looks so happy.
Tor, I said you're lying.
I'm saying "yay". Like this.
Tor didn't say that.
She said "yay!
I'm sure he's smiling.
Okay, Minami.
Next.
Minami?
Minami and Yuzuha are together.
Oh, they're the same.
No way!
You're a liar type.
You always say that.
What are you doing?
I'll take that.
And finally...
Hey, kiddo.
How was it?
Wow!
Not even close.
Slow down.
What the hell?
Isn't it funny how it doesn't get dark until you put them on?
Usually.
The moment they're done.
You were watching her reaction?
It's not funny.
You got me.
I've been set up.
He thinks he's being set up.
Next time, I'm not gonna fall for it.
Next time, I'm out of here.
Next time, everyone's important.
I can't believe we don't have all these.
It's perfect.
There's music.
Of course.
We're not there yet.
I've never been able to get it right.
I've done the peach dance so many times.
I've never had it all come together like this.
It's true that it's surprisingly easy to get it all together.
But you know, Momoka always
I always end up dancing the chorus one more time.
No, no, no...
Where's the rest?
What?
The second verse is still in the same place.
Oh...
You're right, you're right.
Let's do a long one.
Let's do a long song.
Moderator.
So that's it.
Thank you very much for watching!
If you like this video, please subscribe to the channel, give it a high rating, and leave a comment!
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing D-Holic's costume!